{
    "questions":[
        {
            "Question": "I __ with my fingers.",
            "Correct": "Touch",
            "Incorrect1": "Taste",
            "Incorrect2": "Hear",
            "Incorrect3": "Smell"
        },
        {
            "Question":"I __ with my brain.",
            "Correct": "Think",
            "Incorrect1": "Smell",
            "Incorrect2": "See",
            "Incorrect3": "Hear"
        },
        {
            "Question":"Find the verb? >> Sadie raced down the stairs.",
            "Correct": "raced",
            "Incorrect1": "down",
            "Incorrect2": "sadie",
            "Incorrect3": "the"
        },
        {
            "Question":"Find the verb? >> Mom sang along to the pretty music.",
            "Correct": "sang",
            "Incorrect1": "music",
            "Incorrect2": "Mom",
            "Incorrect3": "pretty"
        },
        {
            "Question":"Find the verb? >> Tom ran home after school.",
            "Correct": "ran",
            "Incorrect1": "home",
            "Incorrect2": "Tom",
            "Incorrect3": "after"
        },
        {
            "Question":"__ a horse.",
            "Correct": "ride",
            "Incorrect1": "tell",
            "Incorrect2": "turn on",
            "Incorrect3": "play"
        },
        {
            "Question":"Correct past tense verb >> My mom __ a cake.",
            "Correct":"baked",
            "Incorrect1":"bakes",
            "Incorrect2":"is baking",
            "Incorrect3":"bake"
        },
        {
            "Question":"Alfred __ he had ten marbles.",
            "Correct":"thought",
            "Incorrect1":"thinked",
            "Incorrect2":"thinking",
            "Incorrect3":"think"
        },
        {
            "Question":"Past tense of the word dive",
            "Correct":"dove",
            "Incorrect1":"dave",
            "Incorrect2":"diven",
            "Incorrect3":"dived"
        },
        {
            "Question":"Jerry had __ a fish for dinner.",
            "Correct":"caught",
            "Incorrect1":"caughted",
            "Incorrect2":"caughten",
            "Incorrect3":"catched"
        },
        {
            "Question":"Rose was __ on May 12, 2000.",
            "Correct":"born",
            "Incorrect1":"borne",
            "Incorrect2":"borned",
            "Incorrect3":"bore"
        },
        {
            "Question":"What is the prefix in preheat?",
            "Correct": "pre",
            "Incorrect1": "heat",
            "Incorrect2": "at",
            "Incorrect3": "none "
        },
        {
            "Question":"What is the prefix in mismanage?",
            "Correct": "mis ",
            "Incorrect1": "manage",
            "Incorrect2": "age",
            "Incorrect3": "none"
        },
        {
            "Question":"What is the prefix in prepaid?",
            "Correct": "pre",
            "Incorrect1": "paid",
            "Incorrect2": "both",
            "Incorrect3": "none"
        },
        {
           "Question": "What is the prefix in rematch?",
            "Correct": "re",
            "Incorrect1": "match",
            "Incorrect2": "both",
            "Incorrect3": "none"
        },
        {
           "Question": "What is the prefix in uncover?",
            "Correct": "un",
            "Incorrect1": "cover",
            "Incorrect2": "both",
            "Incorrect3": "none"
        },
        {
           "Question": "What is the prefix in redo?",
            "Correct": "re",
            "Incorrect1": "do",
            "Incorrect2": "both",
            "Incorrect3": "none"
        },
        {
           "Question": "What is the prefix in unfinished?",
            "Correct": "un",
            "Incorrect1": "finished",
            "Incorrect2": "ed",
            "Incorrect3": "none"
        },
        {
           "Question": "What is the prefix in disrespect?",
            "Correct": "dis",
            "Incorrect1": "respect",
            "Incorrect2": "both",
            "Incorrect3": "none"
        },
        {
           "Question": "What is the prefix in forehead?",
            "Correct": "fore",
            "Incorrect1": "head",
            "Incorrect2": "both",
            "Incorrect3": "none"
        },
        {
           "Question": "What is the prefix in dishonor?",
            "Correct": "dis",
            "Incorrect1": "honour",
            "Incorrect2": "both",
            "Incorrect3": "none"
        },
        {
           "Question": "What is the suffix in forgetful?",
            "Correct": "ful",
            "Incorrect1": "forget",
            "Incorrect2": "get",
            "Incorrect3": "none"
        },
        {
           "Question": "What is the suffix in management?",
            "Correct": "ment",
            "Incorrect1": "manage",
            "Incorrect2": "age",
            "Incorrect3": "none"
        },
        {
           "Question": "What is the suffix in useful?",
            "Correct": "ful",
            "Incorrect1": "use",
            "Incorrect2": "both",
            "Incorrect3": "none"
        },
        {
           "Question": "What is the suffix in brotherhood?",
            "Correct": "hood",
            "Incorrect1": "brother",
            "Incorrect2": "both",
            "Incorrect3": "none"
        },
        {
           "Question": "What is the suffix in friendship?",
            "Correct": "ship",
            "Incorrect1": "friend",
            "Incorrect2": "both",
            "Incorrect3": "none"
        },
        {
           "Question": "What is the suffix in comfortable?",
            "Correct": "able",
            "Incorrect1": "comfort",
            "Incorrect2": "both",
            "Incorrect3": "none"
        },
        {
           "Question": "What is the suffix in drinkable?",
            "Correct": "able",
            "Incorrect1": "drink",
            "Incorrect2": "ink",
            "Incorrect3": "none"
        },
        {
           "Question": "What is the suffix in helpful?",
            "Correct": "ful",
            "Incorrect1": "help",
            "Incorrect2": "both",
            "Incorrect3": "none"
        },
        {
          "Question":  "What is the suffix in windy?",
            "Correct": "y",
            "Incorrect1": "wind",
            "Incorrect2": "both ",
            "Incorrect3": "none"
        },
        {
           "Question": "If the computer crashes,____start again.",
            "Correct": "re",
            "Incorrect1": "dis",
            "Incorrect2": "mis ",
            "Incorrect3": "pre"
        },
        {
           "Question": "The company is in chaos due to_____management.",
            "Correct": "mis ",
            "Incorrect1": "dis",
            "Incorrect2": "pre",
            "Incorrect3": "un"
        },
        {
           "Question": "There must be____understanding. I am not  the person your looking for.",
            "Correct": "mis ",
            "Incorrect1": "pre",
            "Incorrect2": "dis",
            "Incorrect3": "un"
        },
        {
           "Question": "Before you bake a cake,___heat the oven.",
            "Correct": "pre",
            "Incorrect1": "dis",
            "Incorrect2": "re",
            "Incorrect3": "un"
        },
        {
           "Question": "We____packeted our bags when we got home.",
            "Correct": "un",
            "Incorrect1": "re",
            "Incorrect2": "pre",
            "Incorrect3": "dis"
        },
        {
            "Question":  "People often____judge with outer looks.",
            "Correct": "mis",
            "Incorrect1": "re",
            "Incorrect2": "dis",
            "Incorrect3": "un"
        },
        {
           "Question": "Since she_____counted, there were too many crayons.",
            "Correct": "mis",
            "Incorrect1": "re",
            "Incorrect2": "dis",
            "Incorrect3": "in"
        },
        {
           "Question": "This book contain a lot of___prints, so I exchanged it.",
            "Correct": "mis",
            "Incorrect1": "in ",
            "Incorrect2": "dis",
            "Incorrect3": "re"
        },
        {
            "Question": "The car crashed because it was_____used.",
            "Correct": "mis",
            "Incorrect1": "dis",
            "Incorrect2": "un ",
            "Incorrect3": "re"
        },
        {
            "Question": "The teacher told me to____write the essay.",
            "Correct": "re",
            "Incorrect1": "dis",
            "Incorrect2": "un",
            "Incorrect3": "mis"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Mr. Jone_____counted the money, so there wasn't enoungh to buy a watch.",
            "Correct": "mis",
            "Incorrect1": "un",
            "Incorrect2": "re",
            "Incorrect3": "in"
        },
        {
            "Question": "He___uses scrap metals to make necklaces.",
            "Correct": "re",
            "Incorrect1": "dis",
            "Incorrect2": "un",
            "Incorrect3": "mis"
        },
        {
           "Question":  "Are there really 14 cups, or did you____count them?",
            "Correct": "mis",
            "Incorrect1": "un ",
            "Incorrect2": "dis ",
            "Incorrect3": "in"
        },
        {
           "Question":  "The movie____starts after a short break.",
            "Correct": "re",
            "Incorrect1": "un",
            "Incorrect2": "in",
            "Incorrect3": "mis"
        },
        {
           "Question":  "After the legohouse fell down, the kids started___building it.",
            "Correct": "re",
            "Incorrect1": "in",
            "Incorrect2": "mis ",
            "Incorrect3": "un"
        },
        {
           "Question":  "Henry dropped out of the college and then____joined the next year.",
            "Correct": "re",
            "Incorrect1": "mis",
            "Incorrect2": "dis ",
            "Incorrect3": "un"
        },
        {
           "Question":  "The criminals tried not to___behave with a Policeman.",
            "Correct": "mis",
            "Incorrect1": "dis",
            "Incorrect2": "un",
            "Incorrect3": "in"
        },
        {
            "Question": "Will you___lock the door for me? I am stuck here.",
            "Correct": "un",
            "Incorrect1": "dis",
            "Incorrect2": "in ",
            "Incorrect3": "re"
        },
        {
           "Question": "If it has been raining for 2 days, it's__safe for travelling.",
            "Correct": "un",
            "Incorrect1": "in ",
            "Incorrect2": "re ",
            "Incorrect3": "dis"
        },
        {
           "Question": "____run the program on my computer and see if it installs this time.",
            "Correct": "re",
            "Incorrect1": "in ",
            "Incorrect2": "dis",
            "Incorrect3": "mis"
        },
        {
           "Question": "Please__think before you make decision.",
            "Correct": "re",
            "Incorrect1": "dis",
            "Incorrect2": "mis ",
            "Incorrect3": "in"
        },
        {
           "Question": "The office is closed now, but it will___open tomorrow.",
            "Correct": "re",
            "Incorrect1": "dis",
            "Incorrect2": "mis ",
            "Incorrect3": "in"
        },
        {
           "Question": "If you___obey my command, you will be removed immediately.",
            "Correct": "dis",
            "Incorrect1": "mis",
            "Incorrect2": "re",
            "Incorrect3": "in"
        },
        {
          "Question":  "She is___happy with her salary.",
            "Correct": "un",
            "Incorrect1": "dis",
            "Incorrect2": "re ",
            "Incorrect3": "in"
        },
        {
           "Question": "__charge your mobile battery if it is under 30 percent.",
            "Correct": "re",
            "Incorrect1": "dis",
            "Incorrect2": "in",
            "Incorrect3": "un"
        },
        {
           "Question": "If the man with the black jacket__appears on the street, catch him.",
            "Correct": "re",
            "Incorrect1": "dis",
            "Incorrect2": "in ",
            "Incorrect3": "un"
        },
        {
           "Question": "She always skips___view of the previous episode.",
            "Correct": "pre",
            "Incorrect1": "dis",
            "Incorrect2": "mis ",
            "Incorrect3": "in"
        },
        {
           "Question": "Even though I__played lecture videos several times, I could not understand. ",
            "Correct": "re",
            "Incorrect1": "dis",
            "Incorrect2": "mis ",
            "Incorrect3": "un"
        },
        {
           "Question": "I took a wrong turn because I___read the sign.",
            "Correct": "mis",
            "Incorrect1": "dis",
            "Incorrect2": "un",
            "Incorrect3": "re"
        },
        {
           "Question": "The Titanic was____covered in 1985.",
            "Correct": "dis",
            "Incorrect1": "re",
            "Incorrect2": "pre",
            "Incorrect3": "in"
        }
    ] 
}
            